<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2016. Saiy Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
  ~
  ~ This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as published
  ~ by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~ GNU Affero General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU Affero General Public License
  ~ along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="title_customisation" translatable="true">Customization</string>
    <string name="error_hotword" translatable="true">"Hotword engine failed to initialize :("</string>
    <string name="menu_synthesised_voice" translatable="true">Google Synthesized Voice</string>

    <string name="notification_initialising_tts" translatable="true">"Initializing TTS"</string>

    <string name="cancelled" translatable="true">"cancelled"</string>
    <string name="analyse" translatable="true">"analyze"</string>
    <string name="vocal_notify_verify" translatable="true">"Okay. I'll notify you know when I've analyzed the audio."</string>


    <string name="bug_content_delay_speech" translatable="true">Text to speech engines take up a lot of resource
        and consequently can take a while to initialize and be ready to speak. This is more common on higher
        quality engines, regardless of whether they are downloaded and installed on the device or not.\n\nIn the
        Superuser Settings, under Memory Usage, you can adjust how long the text to speech engine is bound to
        Saiy and kept in the memory. The longer allowed time, the less likely the initialization process
        will be required for subsequent commands\n\nThis additional memory usage
        should be negligible to the performance of any modern device. If Android needs the memory back,
        it will take it!\n\nIn the Saiy Settings, if you have selected to use the network synthesized voices
        (available via Google\'s text to speech engine), a delay can occur due to the speed of your network
        connection. If your mobile connectivity is a little hit and miss, disabling this feature unless you are
        connected to WiFi, could certainly help…\n\nTap for settings. Tap and hold for Superuser Settings</string>

    <!-- Speech - No command was understood -->
    <string-array name="array_no_comprende" translatable="true">
        <item>"Really sorry %1$s, but I'm not sure what you meant by that."</item>
        <item>"Really sorry, but I'm not sure what you meant by that %1$s."</item>
        <item>"I'm sorry %1$s, but I didn't recognize that command."</item>
        <item>"I'm sorry, but I didn't recognize that command  %1$s."</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Speech - Beyond Verbal - error -->
    <string-array name="array_beyond_verbal_error" translatable="true">
        <item>"Sorry %1$s, but I'm afraid the emotion analysis failed."</item>
        <item>"Sorry %1$s, but I'm afraid I was unable to analyze the emotions of the audio."</item>
        <item>"Apologies %1$s, but I failed to successfully analyze the emotional content."</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Speech - Beyond Verbal -->
    <string-array name="array_beyond_verbal" translatable="true">
        <item>"OK %1$s. I'll be listening."</item>
        <item>"OK %1$s. I'm ready to analyze you."</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="beyond_verbal_extra_verbose" translatable="true">"OK %1$s. In order for me to analyze
        your emotional state, you need to speak for at least thirteen seconds. After that, I'll
        detect when you've finished speaking. You could tell me about your day today, or about a
        memory from your past. If you can't think of anything, just close your eyes and count slowly
        up to fifteen, whilst your mind wanders. I'll let you know with a notification when the
        analysis is complete."</string>

</resources>